Guide to the George McTurnan Kahin papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
Kahin, George McTurnan papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
- Series X. Philippines
  - Agrarian Conditions & Reform, 1977-78 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Military Sales Print Out, 1977-79 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Proposed Extradition Treaty, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Church in Philippines, 1976-78 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Church-State Relations, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Jesuits, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - "Protestant Church in the New Society", 1978 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Corpuz: NLF, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Trinidad Herrera, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Diokno: Philippine Foreign Policy, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Moros, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Republic of the Philippines Newsletter, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Washington D.C.-June 2, 1978 Conference: Church Coalition for H.R. in the Philippines (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Manila (April 5-8-Professional Expenses & Wash(Phil) Duplicates, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Church Coalition: Phil. Expenses/Bill, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Oliver, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Friends of the Filipino People, 1977-79 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Addresses and People: Philippines, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Post Elections April, May, June 1978 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Post Elections, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Developments: June-Dec. 1978 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - State-H.R. Report-Feb. 1979 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Human Rights Political Prisoners, 1976-78 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Sison Statement: May 18, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Political Prisoners, 1978-82 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Possible U.S. Naval Sulu Involvement Nov.-Dec. 1972 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Survey: Religious Superiors-Nov. 26, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Phil. 1946 Taruc (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Philippines-People to See, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Philippines, 1946-74 (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Manglapus, 1975-79 (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - G.K.:CH. on Phil., 1980 (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - P. Quinn-Judge 1979 Reports (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - FFP: 1979 (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - F.F.P.-K.D.P. Split, 1979-81 (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - McArthur's 500,000, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - Philippines-Parker M. Borg, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - Philippines, 1972-77 (Box 64, Folder 43)
  - Political Detainees Update & CHRP, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 44)
- Series XI. Publications: Southeast Asia
  - Richard Baron, 1970-84 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Lary Malley & Taylor on Presses, 1983-84 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Letter to Editors, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Harper & Row, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Free Press, 1979-84 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Alfred Knopf, 1984-85 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Houghton Mifflin, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Norton, 1975-84 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Westview, 1976-80 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Princeton, 1977-86 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Other Press Expressing Interest, 1975-77 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Vantage Press, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Nolting MS-University of Virginia, 1986-89 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - PRRI, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Press: Nationalism and Revolution, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Press: Royalties for G.K., 1969-86 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University Press, 1966-73 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Macandrews-CU Press, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Bob Johnson, 1977-78 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Ricklefs, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Press, Davis: Laos & Leifer, 1974-75 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Press, 1979-80 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - M. Ricklefs, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Press, 1976-78 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Nationalism & Revolution in Indonesia Translations, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Bedlington, 1973-76 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Bedlington, 1975-77 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Colbert, 1974-82 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Anderson-Indonesia, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - C.U. Press-Advertising SEA Series, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Cornell Press SEA Series: Forward, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Harold Crouch, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - H. Crouch, 1976-88 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Feith-Suharto-SEA Series, 1973-76 (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Lev-Indonesia SEA Series, 1974-80 (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - C.U. Press: SEA Series, 1969-80 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Porter: Vietnam, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - Porter-Vietnam, 1974-87 (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - Smith, 1973-75 (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - Silverstein, 1974-78 (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - Silverstein, 1977-79 (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Wilson, 1972-76 (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Weinstein, 1971-75 (Box 65, Folder 43)
  - Weinstein, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 44)
  - Wurfel, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 45)
  - Girling: Thailand, 1976-80 (Box 65, Folder 46)
  - Girling, 1980-84 (Box 65, Folder 47)
  - Girling: Super Power & World Disorder, 1984-88 (Box 65, Folder 48)
  - Wurfel: Philippines, 1974-87 (Box 65, Folder 49)
  - Robert McMahon, 1945-49 (Box 65, Folder 50)
  - Final N.E.H. Report June 6, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 51)
  - SEATO-GK Testimony, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 52)
  - New SEATO Article, 1974-79 (Box 65, Folder 53)
  - SEATO-Present Status, 1975-79 (Box 65, Folder 54)
  - SEATO Data, 1966-77 (Box 65, Folder 55)
  - SEATO: Malaysian Question, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 56)
  - SEATO, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 57)
  - S.E.A.T.O., 1954-73 (Box 65, Folder 58)
  - SEATO-Library of Congress, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 59)
  - SEATO, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 60)
  - SEATO: End & Retrospect, 1975-76 (Box 65, Folder 61)
  - SEATO-Oct. 13, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 62)
  - SEATO, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 63)
  - New Republic: SEAT Oct. 14, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 64)
  - Paukev-SEA, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 65)
  - CIA: Congressional Oversight, 1972-75 (Box 65, Folder 66)
  - Publications & Lectures for Courses
    - Opium & Heroin-SEA, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - SEA Regionalism, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Senate Foreign Relations Committee, 1958-75 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Congress & Foreign Policy, 1972-74 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Com. on the Organization of the Government for the Conduct of Foreign Policy, 1972-74 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Containment, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - U.S. & India, Pakistan, 1969-73 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Britain & Commonwealth, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - McCarthy & (ism), n.d. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - ABM: China, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - China, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - U.S. & China, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Japan & U.S., 1967-72 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Quemoy & Matsu, 1958-59 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Korea, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Lebanon, 1957-59 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Soviet-Asia Policy, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Communism in Asia, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Revolution, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Development & Politics, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - National Integration-Ideas, 1963-72 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - CIA, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - U.S. Policy-Intelligence, 1958-77 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - "A" Exams & "B" Exams, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Exams and Grading, 1979-80 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Theses, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Government Indochina Search Committee, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Language and Statistics, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Government Curriculum for Discussion-Dec. 13, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Government :Current, 1977-79 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Government Dept: Administration, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Government-Seminars, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Courses-including 300's, 1975-81 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Enrollments of Courses & Seminars, 1974-75 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Courses and Seminar Enrollments, 1980-81 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Ethics & Public Life, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - "A" Exams, 1982-88 (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Government Department Members, 1973-74 (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Admissions, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Comparative Government Search, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Government Enrollments-Spring, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Government Courses, 1977-84 (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - International Relations, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 43)
    - International Relations, 1982-88 (Box 66, Folder 44)
    - I.R. Memo, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 45)
    - I.R. Exams, 1981-86 (Box 66, Folder 46)
    - Feb. 22-I.R. Exam, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 47)
    - I.R. Exams, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 48)
    - Government: Priorities Committee, 1986-87 (Box 66, Folder 49)
    - Chairmanship, 1986-87 (Box 66, Folder 50)
    - 417-Exams, 1961-62 (Box 66, Folder 51)
    - The United States and Asia-Class List, Government 417, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 52)
    - 417-Class Folder, 1960-62 (Box 66, Folder 53)
    - Government 417-Reading Lists, 1950-60 (Box 66, Folder 54)
    - Government 417-Reading Lists, 1945-60 (Box 66, Folder 55)
    - 377-Reading Lists, 1962-64 (Box 66, Folder 56)
    - 377-Papers, 1963-64 (Box 66, Folder 57)
    - 377-Map Quiz, 1951-66 (Box 66, Folder 58)
    - Government 377-Class List/Lectures, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 59)
    - 417 Class Lists, 1951-60 (Box 66, Folder 60)
    - Seminar 644, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 61)
    - 644, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 62)
    - Seminar 577, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 63)
    - Government-396, 1955-56 (Box 66, Folder 64)
    - Government 395, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 65)
    - Government 417 (Fall 1952) Best Take Home Exam Answers, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 66)
    - Reading Lists, 1956-66 (Box 66, Folder 67)
    - Government 377, 1963-64 (Box 66, Folder 68)
    - 417-Map Quiz, 1959-61 (Box 66, Folder 69)
    - U.S. Foreign Policy, 1949-60 (Box 66, Folder 70)
    - Grades 417, 1951-60 (Box 66, Folder 71)
    - Government 417-Lectures, 1957-60 (Box 66, Folder 72)
    - Government 417-Papers (ideas), n.d. (Box 66, Folder 73)
    - Government 417-Class Materials, 1949-56 (Box 66, Folder 74)
    - Major Governments Criticisms (Indonesia Sectoin & Suggestions) (Box 66, Folder 75)
    - Major Governments Suggestions, 1958-59 (Box 66, Folder 76)
    - ADDENDA (not incorporated but useful) (Box 66, Folder 77)
- Series XII. Cambodia (Laos & Thailand)
  - Cambodia: Addresses, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Cambodia, 1967-75 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Cambodia (continued), 1969-70 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Cambodia, 1985-91 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Cambodia-Annual Review from PRO, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Salim House, Daniel Boone, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Sihanouk & U.S.-Dawn Draayer, 1967-69 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Cambodia-Miscellaneous, 1951-75 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Dap Chuon-from PRO, April 1959 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Dap Chuon, 1958-70 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Cambodia-National Archives, 1958-65 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Matsumoto-Foreign Policy, 1965-67 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Cambodia's Perspective on Vietnam War-Weinstein, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Khmer Issarak, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Khieu Samphan, 1975-76 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Khmer Serei, 1967-79 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Son Ngoc Thanh, 1971-72 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Burhan Magenda (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Cambodia, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Cabinets, 1945-70 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Laura Summers, 1953-60 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - GK (Paul Johnson) Border-August 9, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - 1967 Interviews-Cambodia (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Cambodia M.S.: April 1997 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Cambodia: Budgets, 1967-71 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - 1967-1969, 1967-69 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Coup of March 1970, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - D.O.D.-Cooper/U.S., 1966 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - DIA-Cooper, 1970-78 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Cambodia-U.N., 1969 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Briefing, Congressional Staff March 18, 1970 Marshall Green (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - State Department Documents, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - U.S. Involvemnt in Coup, 1970-86 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - CIA-DIA: Advance Knowledge of Coup, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Daniel Roy-Le Monde Diplomatique, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - HDS-Greenway-Atlantic, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - Allman File, 1970-71 (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - Coup: March 1970, 1970-82 (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - Course of Coup, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Donald Lancarter, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - General Accounts, 1970-88 (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Cambodia: British Records, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Declassified Docs. References Service, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Church Com., 1982 (Box 67, Folder 44)
  - Peking View of U.S.-Cambodian Relations, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - Chronologies, 1972-86 (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Articles-Non NYT, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - NY Times 1970-Some very important (Box 67, Folder 48)
  - Newspaper Clippings + Articles-Cambodia, 1967-69 (Box 67, Folder 49)
  - Cambodia Clippings, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 50)
  - Cambodia, Press Clippings, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 51)
  - 1970-Post Coup, 1970-96 (Box 67, Folder 52)
  - Don Noel, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 53)
  - Thornton: re Coup, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 54)
  - Columbia Eagle, 1970-75 (Box 67, Folder 55)
  - Norfolk-Virginia Pilot, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 56)
  - January 1970 (Box 67, Folder 57)
  - Post Coup: March-April, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 58)
  - Cambodian Invasion Violates International Law May 18, 1979, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 59)
  - GK: US Senate May 7-14, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 60)
  - Nixon's Decision, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 61)
  - Q & A, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 62)
  - Cambodia-Dept. of State Questions & Answers: May 1970 (Box 67, Folder 63)
  - Saigon's Reactions to Events in Cambodia May 1970 (Box 67, Folder 64)
  - Cambodia: U.S.-Saigon Invasion, Spring 1970 (Box 67, Folder 65)
  - Cambodia-May 1970 (Box 67, Folder 66)
  - Cambodia (Press and Articles), 1970-71 (Box 67, Folder 67)
  - PRG Statement on Cambodia, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 68)
  - Consequences of the Invasion of Cambodia, Kahin, May 14, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 69)
  - G.K.-Senate-Cambodia, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 70)
  - Chronology-Cornell CCAS, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 71)
  - 1970(June) - 1974 Chronology by U.S. Embassy-P.P. (Carney), 1976 (Box 67, Folder 72)
  - Cambodia & Laos
    - Lon Nul Coup: Indonesian Role, 1967-74 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Thai Military Support, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Cambodia & Interview Notes, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Phnom Penh, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Cambodia-Important, 1976-78 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Cambodia-POST, 1980-97 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Cambodia Feb. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - 1989-Cambodia: U.S.-U.N. Pol. Pot., 1980-90 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Cambodia Clippings, 1990-92 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Cambodia, 1989-90 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Extra Copies of Important Docs Used in Book, 1964-76 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Cambodia: Addenda, 1967-78 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Cambodia Chapter-Disk, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Indochina Com Party-Critical Evaluation, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Cambodia Fact Sheet, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Duplicates: Cambodia, 1967-71 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Cambodia Notes-Duplicates, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Cambodia Notes-August 1971 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Cambodia, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Cambodia-Correspondence & Logisitics, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Cambodia-Political, 1970-74 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Berhin Magenda-Cambodia & Laos, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Cambodia, Military Balance-U.S. & Foreign Relations, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Unconstitutionality of U.S. Military Actions, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Cambodia & U.S. Intervention, 1973-74 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Nixon & Cambodia, 1977-79 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Cambodia: Debate over Secret Bombing of 1969-70, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Cambodia Bombing, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Cambodia: Settlement?, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - General Assembly Vote, 1974-75 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Senate Hearing March 6, 1975 & Background Material (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Cambodia, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Cambodia, 1975-78 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Khmer Rouge, 1967-75 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Cambodia, 1970-75 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Kennedy Com. Report, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - G.K. Drafts, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - Cambodia: Article Drafts & Material Useful for Articles, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - Mayaguez, 1975-76 (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - Laura Summers, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 40)
    - The Chams of Cambodia, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 41)
    - Cambodia: Hearings Feb. 24 & March 6, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 42)
    - Laos: New Data in C. U. (Box 68, Folder 43)
    - Thailand: Information Bulletin: Paris 1976-77, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 44)
    - Lou Kubicka, 1976-77 (Box 68, Folder 45)
    - Chester Cooper, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 46)
    - Laos, 1954-83 (Box 68, Folder 47)
    - Laotian Fact Sheet & Vietnam, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 48)
    - Branfman, 1970-75 (Box 68, Folder 49)
    - U.S. & Laos, 1961-70 (Box 68, Folder 50)
    - Winthrop Brown, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 51)
    - Alveigh Burke re 1961 Kennedy, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 52)
    - Laos: U.S. Government, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 53)
    - Laos Interviews, 1967-76 (Box 68, Folder 54)
    - Laos Articles, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 55)
    - Burma Notes-Duplicates, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 56)
    - Thailand 1976-Duplicates (Box 68, Folder 57)
    - Laos, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 58)
    - Laos-Duplicates, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 59)
    - Laos Interviews, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 60)
    - Laos-Press Clippings, 1968-69 (Box 68, Folder 61)
    - Laos-P.L. Negotiating Position, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 62)
    - Laos: 1972-1973, 1972-73 (Box 68, Folder 63)
    - Laos, 1968-70 (Box 68, Folder 64)
    - Laos: Secret War in 1972 (Box 68, Folder 65)
    - Laos & U.S. Policy, 1972-73 (Box 68, Folder 66)
    - Clippings-Laos, 1969-74 (Box 68, Folder 67)
    - Laos, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 68)
    - Laos, 1971-76 (Box 68, Folder 69)
    - Laos-Press Clippings, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 70)
    - Laos-Refugees, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 71)
    - Ramsay: U.S. Influence on Domestic Politics of Laos, 1957-62 (Box 68, Folder 72)
    - CIA in Laos, 1961-75 (Box 68, Folder 73)
    - U.S. Influence on Laotian Politics, 1961-73 (Box 68, Folder 74)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959-61 (Box 68, Folder 75)
    - Laos, 1961-62 (Box 68, Folder 76)
    - Winthrop Brown, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 77)
    - Mary Pasti, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 78)
    - Laos: Official Pubblications, 1959-70 (Box 68, Folder 79)
    - Laos, 1969-72 (Box 68, Folder 80)
    - Laos-Davis, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 89)
  - Cambodia & Thailand
    - Miscellaneous-Cambodia, 1973-95 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous-Cambodia (continued), 1992 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Declassified Docs. Reference System, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Library: Map, 1973-83 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Maphilindo Notes, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Malaysia-Manila Conference: August 29, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Indonesia & Malaysia Trip: Original Notes and Top Copies, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Thailand-Maps (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Thailand: Bibliography, 1959-76 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Thailand Constitution and Cabinet-Dec. 1972 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Thailand-Fact Sheet and Map, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Thailand Clippings, 1964-72 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - KMT: Thailand, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - KMT China & Siam, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Thailand, 1950-69 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Thailand: JFK, 1961-75 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Thailand, 1971-72 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Thailand Pre 1970, 1967-69 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Hill Tribes, 1973-75 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Vietnamese in Thailand-Nakornthab (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - War in N. THailand-Jeffrey Race, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Thai Communists, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Thailand-Cambodia, 1970-72 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Thailand, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Thailand: Military Sales, 1976-78 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - East Asian Advisory Panel, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Surachart's Reference to Docs on Thailand, 1982-83 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Thai-U.S., 1945-57 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Thailand: Insurgencies-Notes, 1967-69 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Thailand-Interviews Etc., 1955-70 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Notes: Thailand, June 1972 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Philippines/Bases, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Thailand 1976-Duplicates (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Thailand-SEATO, 1970-76 (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - Thailand-Clippings, 1980-92 (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - 1976:Notes-Thailand (Box 69, Folder 36)
    - Thailand, 1961-75 (Box 69, Folder 37)
    - LBJ-Thailand New?, 1975-85 (Box 69, Folder 38)
    - Thailand & U.S.-Tomseth, 1972-76 (Box 69, Folder 39)
    - Thai Attitudes Towards the U.S., 1969-73 (Box 69, Folder 40)
    - U.S. in Thailand, 1969-74 (Box 69, Folder 41)
    - Fraser Committee, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - Ltr. to Kikrit, Siam Rath 12-26-67, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - Thailand-Press and Documents, 1967-71 (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - Thailand, 1973-75 (Box 69, Folder 45)
    - Press, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 46)
    - Thailand-Girling, 1969-72 (Box 69, Folder 47)
    - 1976 Material (Box 69, Folder 48)
    - U.S. Invovlvement in Thailand Conference, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 49)
    - Rusk-Thanat/Reagan on 1981, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 50)
    - Thailand Letters, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 51)
    - Keyes Letter, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 52)
    - Clippings, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 53)
    - Thailand: Coup of Oct. 6, 1976 & Aftermath, 1976-77 (Box 69, Folder 54)
    - 13-3/77 to 31-3/77 Good Material, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 55)
    - NY Times Letter-Nov. 2, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 56)
    - Novanit Setabutr, 1976-77 (Box 69, Folder 57)
    - East-West Center-Feb. 14, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 58)
    - Thailand: Current, 1977-79 (Box 69, Folder 59)
    - Thailand State Department-H.R., 1979 (Box 69, Folder 60)
    - Thailand Article-G.K., 1976 (Box 69, Folder 61)
    - Girling-P.A., 1977 (Box 69, Folder 62)
    - Data for Article-Class I, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 63)
- Series XIII. Vietnam
  - Trip:Jan, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Thailand (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Singapore (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Saigon (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Vietnam (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Widyono (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Anthony Eden (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Vietnam-Notes Jan 1967 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Interviews 1966-7, 1966-1967 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Return to US 1967 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - 1967 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Fulbright Memo:March 20, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - C.K. Report to Senators/March 20, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - General Pham Xuan Chieu, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Dr. Phan Quang Dan, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Vietnam Visit to First Corps Area, Jan1967 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Newspaper Clips (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - New Republic-Unpublished, Oct 1972 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Vietnam (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Hanoi-Interviews (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - North Vietnam, August, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Ha Van Lau, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - NLF-Interviews 1967-1972 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Soai (PRG) 1971 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Sullivan, Oct10, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - cable (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - comments: Alan, George, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - 1966: Important (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Elections (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Tet & Post Tet (1968): D. Elliott WGBH Critique (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - GK Paris, Sept 1968 (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - GK Paris, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - Manac'h Paris 1968 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - Buddhist Crisis: Mid-1966 (Box 73, Folder 34)
    - Buddhist 1966 (Box 73, Folder 35)
    - U.S. efforts to control and divide the Buddhists, 1965-1966 (Box 73, Folder 36)
    - Relevant Interviews (Box 73, Folder 37)
    - US involvement in South Vietnam Suppression of Buddhists-Spring 1966 (Box 73, Folder 38)
  - Most Important Documents JFK Vietnam (Box 73, Folder 39)
    - Vietnam-General (Box 73, Folder 40)
  - GK/Bundy Debate:1965 (Box 73, Folder 41)
  - Elections (Box 73, Folder 42)
    - Local Elections, May30, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 43)
    - Constituent Assembly, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 44)
    - Bill Bundy on Elections, August, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 45)
    - Election/U.S. role, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 46)